{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_9_OZSXDL",
                "player_4_OZSXDL",
                "player_11_OZSXDL",
                "player_12_OZSXDL"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                9,
                4,
                11,
                12
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone.",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -47183.679,
                    15558.913,
                    -22529.287,
                    0,
                    148.9571333630086,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -46820.137,
                    15667.776,
                    -22522.583,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -47002.764,
                    15661.741,
                    -22529.288,
                    0,
                    -153.81929831909918,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -46893.666,
                    16298.279,
                    -22526.457,
                    0,
                    -3.003728309589718,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -46968.011,
            15811.556,
            -22525.937
        ],
        "sample_radius": 692.3684881813622
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -46384.142,
            16494.089,
            -22529.288,
            0,
            -130.27472703036605,
            0
        ],
        [
            -47239.464,
            14920.05,
            -22523.13,
            0,
            73.2159867260232,
            0
        ],
        [
            -45907.722,
            15817.57,
            -23446.428,
            0,
            -178.87860091267183,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are visible within the scene, encompassing both the ancient ruins and the dark chamber?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Among all the individuals present, how many are identified as men?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Among all the individuals present, how many are identified as women?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are noted to have a medium skin complexion?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Excluding the person who is standing, how many individuals are in other distinct postures?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are actively engaged in picking something up?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many people are wearing glasses in the scene?",
                "answer": "zero"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many people with bald heads are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "zero"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding something",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding something"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. standing"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. crouching"
                ],
                "answer": "A. lying down"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            }
        }
    }
}